Nobody runs forever
The Mule is a crime, drama film directed by Clint Eastwood.
Earl Stone, a man in his eighties, is broke, alone, and facing foreclosure of his
business when he is offered a job that simply requires him to drive.
Easy enough, but, unbeknownst to Earl, he's just signed on
as a drug courier for a Mexican cartel.
He does so well that his cargo increases exponentially, and Earl hit
the radar of hard-charging DEA agent Colin Bates.
Earl Stone, played by Clint Eastwood.
Agent Colin Bates, played by Bradley Cooper.
Special Agent in Charge, played by Laurence Fishburne.
Agent Treviño, played by Michael Peña.
Mary, played by Dianne Wiest.
Latón, played by Andy Garcia.
The Mule is a 2018 American crime drama film starring and directed by Clint Eastwood, and produced by
Eastwood, Dan Friedkin, Jessica Meier, Tim Moore, Kristina Rivera, and Bradley Thomas.
The screenplay, written by Nick Schenk, is based on the 2014 The New York Times article "The Sinaloa Cartel's 90-Year-Old Drug Mule" by Sam
Dolnick, which recounts the story of Leo Sharp, a World War II  veteran in his 80s who became a drug courier for the Sinaloa Cartel.
The film co-stars Bradley Cooper, Laurence Fishburne,
Michael Peña, Dianne Wiest, and Andy García.
This was Eastwood's first acting project since 2012, and his first
starring leading role in a film directed by himself since 2008.
Filming began in early June 2018, taking place in Atlanta and Augusta,
Georgia, with other film locations in Las Cruces, New Mexico.
The Mule was released in the United States on December 14, 2018, by Warner Bros.
It grossed over $174 million.
The film received generally positive reviews, with critics calling it
"poignant and charming" and praising Eastwood's performance.
The film explores themes of mexico, drug crime,
texas, drug mule, based on true story.
The tone is emotional.